I'm just coming on here very quickly to ask a very basic question.
When are people going to realize that the only version of the world that we want to live in will be created by us?
I am so sick of hearing folks saying so-and-so needs to be tried in The Hague.
I am so sick of hearing this is a war crime.
Wake the fuck up.
Wake up.
First of all, you're really talking about The Hague in 2026, the year of the old gods and the new?
You're still acting as if The Hague was some legitimate source of justice?
When you know full well that Nazis were hired by NASA?
When you know full well that Nazis were sent in droves to Argentina?
When you know full well that George Bush Sr. hired Nazis?
When you know full well that the third highest ranking Nazi in the United States was actually Jewish?
Like, this pisses me off because I'm just like, how?
How?
There's just too much information.
And at what point do Americans get to stop being considered, well, they're just dumb?
At what point?
At what point do y'all really understand?
Like, hey, you know, it really is our responsibility to switch this up.
Like, niggas really sat there at Jesse Jackson's funeral and listened to war criminals, like actual imperialists, use the man's funeral as a platform, as a bully pulpit, as a dais, if you will.
Genociders.
Active genociders.
When I hear y'all talk about, this is a war crime, this is against international law, these people need to be tried to hate, people that are smart, people that are knowledgeable, people that are learned.
I'm like, huh?
Not now.
Not in this year.
No.
You can't be.
You can't.
And let me just tell you, you know, you hear a lot of folks talking about the earth splitting into two.
You hear a lot of spiritualists talking about, like, these are times that are splitting into two and we're not all going to be in the same world.
And, you know, when they see that, when you say this, when they say this, you're like, what does that look like?
Like, how does that exist?
What does that mean?
And I'm just like, you know, what my fury, what my passion is right now, I want you to know this is not aligned to like,
Oh, I'm mad about people.
It's more so just like, I wish, I wish for, for a stronger army to fight.
I want us to be stronger.
I want us to be, to be tapped in to, to all that has been laid before us.
And to, to, to, to, to do that, you're going to have, look at this damn cat, Mando.
And to do that, you're going to have to wake the fuck up.
Like talking about the Hague at this point is so, it's so bonkers to me because I'm like, okay, so just so I'm clear, you're expecting the colonizers to bring the colonizers to justice.
Like when I see people say shit, like they should sue, or when I see people say shit, like, Oh, you know, um, they, they, they need to be arrested.
I'm just like, you're missing the point.
You know, who needs to be arrested?
Kamala Harris, Joe Biden, Barack Obama, Bill Clinton.
Yeah.
They need to be arrested.
If we're talking about arrested and instead y'all are at Jesse Jackson's funeral.
Applauding, like, that's right.
They should call her.
I'm like, and so ever so often I have to vent all of this out.
No, no.
Trump should not be arrested.
That would be too kind.
When I speak, understand my words are chosen very carefully.
So I, I, I have to vent and I have to like, get all this out of my system so that I can continue to do the work of spirituality, the work of high vibration, the work of love.
Look at him.
Absolutely ridiculous.
So, you know, that's why I have to like, come on here sometimes and just, I have to just, I just have to do it because I'm, I'm just, I'm, I'm like, I'm, I'm cleansing.
I'm cleansing.
Tell your cat I said.
So that's my words.
You know, someone saying, why should they be arrested?
What crime have they committed?
And this is the type of thing I'm looking, I'm talking about.
Y'all, please help that person out.
What crime have Kamala Harris, Joe Biden, Bill Clinton, and Barack Obama committed?
What crime singular?
Everything you're seeing that's happening in Venezuela, everything you're seeing that's happening in Iran, everything you're seeing that you're like, oh my God, that's crazy.
How could they do that?
They can't just go in there and take out somebody.
They've done it.
They did it in Libya.
They did it in Honduras.
They did it in Guatemala.
Yeah.
We didn't have the internet at that time.
So a lot of shit was able to go under the, under the, um, under the, the radar.
George Bush Jr.
Arrested.
Go up down, go down in hell and get both, uh, George Bush Sr. up here.
NAFTA.
Iraq.
I can go on and on and on.
Yemen.
Somalia.
There's, there, there are so many egregious crimes that these people have committed.
All in the name of the United States.
And you will tell yourself they did this to protect us.
No, they did not.
No, they didn't.
And they sat up there at that man's funeral.
And y'all sat up there and clapped.
Yeah, yeah.
Disgusting.
Absolutely.
Abu Ghraib.
Disgusting.
So may we all continue to awaken our spirits, our minds, and our souls.
May we all continue to find ourselves in alignment with community and with the land.
May we all continue to create connectivity with comrades across the world.
Jonas Couch.
I don't know why you're asking me such a dumb question.
There is no plan for fixing the United States.
May the United States perish and burn.
And may them, as many of us as possible, survive to build something better.
And I found my mic mount.
I need y'all to know that I found my mic mount.
And this is a very big deal.
Because I need to record vocals today if I'm going to get regulated.
Because I am very dysregulated right now.
And I was like, really?
And it smells like mouse excrement.
So I have to clean it.
Because there were definitely mice that were taking up refuge in my storage cabinet.
Which I'm completely fine with.
However, I found my mic mount.
And I was about to drive to Guitar Center.
Because the mom and pop shop by around my way did not have a shock mount.
And I was about to get in the car.
I was about to drive to Guitar Center.
And because I had almost infallible intuition.
My intuition said, skrrt, skrrt.
Don't do that.
Don't go to Yonkers on a Sunday.
You're going to find your mic mount.
So I looked in three different places.
I went to my storage unit.
And then I said, I got one more place I'm going to look.
One more place.
And then I was still, I was still going to walk out.
I was still going to give up.
And then I said, man, stop being lazy and turn on the flashlight on the phone.
And here it is.
I found it.
So I'm about to go lay down vocals.
Someone said it's a mice mount.
Fair.
This is the time to start going down rabbit holes.
You need to understand that this is the time for you to blow your own mind before they blow it for you.
You hear me?
Blow your own mind before they blow it for you.
Some of y'all are really afraid to die, which is amazing to me because for your fear of dying, you are so active in not living.
For folks who are so afraid of dying, we got a lot of people that are more afraid of living.
So it would behoove you to use the portals of information that are available to you.
Again, not everything necessarily is true.
Again, not everything is necessarily fleshed out.
Again, you don't have to receive or understand everything, but you need to blow your own mind.
You need to ask the question, well, who are the Jews?
The same way that you've been asking who are the Christians, who are the Jews?
Are there fake Muslims?
Were there giants?
What's the great reset?
What's in our food?
Why did people in the 1700s and 1800s live to 100, but we're living to 65?
Ancient civilizations mapping stars and we're acting like shit is brand new.
Need for the Revolutionary War.
What is MKUltra?
Are there tunnels under the world?
Why is it 64 degrees today and the snow isn't melting?
Why is it 64 degrees and the snow isn't melting?
Questions upon questions upon questions.
Yeah.
Snow.
Why am I looking at snow?
It's rained.
Why is there still snow?
So, again, what part of the world is this?
New York.
Why is there still fucking snow on my ground?
No, the ground is not frozen.
I walked on the ground today with my bare feet.
It is not frozen.
It's actually hot as fuck.
No, it's not cold.
It's just there.
DeBose, you're about to get blocked because you're annoying me.
Same.
7.30 all day?
I came outside and I was like, God damn, it's like 64 degrees right now.
And it was 64 degrees.
God is still in control.
God can heal and redeem the world.
Who the fuck do y'all even think God is?
When y'all say shit like that, I'd be wondering, like, who do y'all think God is?
Who do you think God is?
That's the problem.
They convinced you that God is somebody but you.
And so you sitting here twiddling your thumbs.
Let me get off this goddamn app.
I'm going to make some music.
You all have a good day.